xinxii.com 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy | XinXii - GD Publishing Ltd. & Co. KG

[THIS IS FOR XINXII SECTION]

Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is a priority at XinXii and we want you to be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and of your choices. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time.

### The information we collect

We get personal information when you visit XinXii pages, when you register with XinXii, when you use services on XinXii and when you contact us. The types of personal information that may be collected on our pages are: name, company name, title, gender, address, birth date, e-mail address, phone number, fax number or credit card information.

### The way we use personal information

XinXii uses personal information that you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide the features and services found on the XinXii Platform. When you purchase a download, your information will be stored on our system to complete the buying process. It must be shared with an outside party in order to verify your credit card information.

Additionally we may contact you via e-mail to send you the XinXii newsletter, to communicate updates, for customer service purposes (e.g. if you have questions about your orders), or to communicate about any content that you have uploaded to the XinXii Platform.

XinXii does not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their marketing or promotional uses.

Please be aware that any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on the XinXii Platform (e.g. your author profile) becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction.

### Cookies Information

To function correctly, the XinXii Platform requires your Internet browser to accept cookies. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide business and marketing information to the owners of the site.

Cookies are small strings of text that can be read only by the site which originally delivered the cookie. Cookies do not contain any (personal) information retrieved from your computer; they only contain information supplied during your specific visit to the site sending the cookie.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

If you wish to find out more about how to control cookies in your web browser, please see [this website](http://www.aboutcookies.org/how-to-control-cookies/).

### Data Security

XinXii follows security standards, processes and procedures that are designed to protect your personal information. All user data are 256-bit SSL encrypted, so that they are safe and unauthorized unreadable to us. NOTE: You are responsable for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times.

### Right to revocation, modification and deletion

You may decline to share your personal information with XinXii. You may update, correct, or delete your user information and preferences at any time at [privacy@xinxii.com](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@xinxii.com)

### Third Party Sites

The XinXii Platform may contain links to third party websites, which are not under the control of XinXii. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any third party website.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

For further questions please contact us at [privacy@xinxii.com](https://mail.google.com/mail/?view=cm&fs=1&tf=1&to=privacy@xinxii.com)
